Hello, friends.
Welcome to this course in this course.
We will be learning Gatsby and Graphql, and we will create a blog website.
So are there any course requirements or prerequisite?
To work on this project, you must have the following skill sets, you should have basic knowledge of
HTML, basic knowledge of CSIS and basic knowledge of JavaScript.
Course objectives, participants will be able to implement their Gatsbyjs and graphql concept in
their current and future projects what you will learn in this course, we will create a blog website
using Gastby and graphql.
And for styling, we will be using style components who are the target of students, students with no
Gatsby and graphql experience, front end developers and anyone who wants to learn Gatsby and graphql
in.
By the end of the course, you will have the following skill set hands on regarding practical and real
life scenario of creating a blog using Gatsby and graphql.
So let's get started and I'll see you in the next video.