Hello, friends, in this lecture, we will talk about what good speech is, is, and the best place
to check is the official website, which is that speech is dot com.
It has everything that you need to know about gas, which is there.
Documentation is amazing.
It is the best documentation.
It goes everything.
So you can see it, says one friend, Ben, to rule them all.
This is our tag line that Gadsby uses on their site.
And this is true because we can build blazing fast website and apps using Gadsby.
So why are these sites so fast?
That's because they are static.
And what a static site, a site which has only admin access and little bit of JavaScript and no database.
And this is exactly what Gadsby will do for us.
It will create static SDM and Cyesis and JavaScript files for us.
And you don't have any connection with that database and that's why it is so fast.
This also means that you have some restriction when you create sites with Gadsby, because, for example,
if you have a site that is going to have a lot of dynamic data, a lot of calls to database and API
and stuff like that, maybe Gadsby won't be the best choice for you if you have a site that's going
to update the data every minute or so.
But actually you can build everything with Gadsby because Gadsby will by default recognize those things
which need to be dynamic.
And you can create a site with mixed dynamic content and static content.
Gadsby will create admin files, ccis and just to file for you, that's not connected to any data base
or stuff like that, you can just copy that to the server and get up and running.
That's why it is so fast.
And that is why you need to have a little bit of different workflow.
If you have, for example, a blog that you are going to update with different blog posts and stuff
like that, like, for example, in WordPress, you change your post to create a new post and then you
publish it and it is published.
But you cannot do that with Gadsby because when you change the data, the site have to be rebuilt.
And this, depending on the size of the site, will take different time.
I hope you understood what Gadsby is because it's B really is a static site generator.
It will create static files for you.
So you have to think in another way and not in the WordPress way where you always make requests to the
database.
And you can also source data from anywhere into Gadsby.
That means you can have different content management systems where you can have markdown as we are going
to use this in our post and you can grab it from different APIs.
So it is really flexible in that way.
And then it builds the site.
And internally, Gadsby uses graphical and react.
And that's what we are going to be using in our course.
And Gadsby is actually a really good way to learn and react and graphical.
But I would say you should have some basic knowledge of react and maybe a little bit of graphics, because
I will not go into details on how react works and how graphical works.
We will look at it and I will explain stuff, but I will not go into details on every aspect, for example,
on REAC.
So this is it.
So please visit Gadsby website and go through the documentation so you will have a basic knowledge before
you start the schools.
So this is a big Northcoast for Gadsby, but not for the and graphical.
So I'll see you in the next video.