I love to start working on Gatsby.
We will use Gatsby to bootstrap The Gatsby side, so we need to go to the official website, which is
Gatsby, James Dotcom, and we need to go to dogs and inside we need to click on QuickStart.
OK, so these are the steps to create a Gatsby website.
So instead of the steps I will use and be X and be X will help us to get the latest version of Gatsby.
When you bootstrap your application and that's great.
So that is one advantage of using antiques so you can do whatever you want.
If you want to follow the step, you can follow this or else you can follow what I am doing, ok.
I'll be using antiques so to use and and we need to go to Israel studio.
OK, so we need a good editor.
I am using Visual Studio Code.
If you don't have visual studio would just Google it as a and this is the FirstLine.
So you need to install this, OK, so this is Warmack, and if you are a Windows user, you just need
to click on this arrow and you need to download and install it and even you need to install JS.
OK, so your.
Is the Narges website, and if you are a Mac user, just click on this Altius Virgin and if you are
a Windows user, just go to download and your the options.
OK, so just click and install it.
So there's two things you required.
OK, so now I'll go to a little studio code, which is my code editor and you're I'll open the terminal
by pressing control and practically OK, which is about the you and I want to create my website on desktop.
So let me go to my desktop, which is next stop.
Now I'm inside my desktop and I will write the command and be X Gadsby's.
New, this new keyword will create a site for us and I'll keep the name of my Web site as speech and
blog.
OK, because we are creating a blog Web site, you can keep whatever name you want, OK?
And I'll press enter.
So it will take some time.
So now everything is in and we need to navigate inside the folder, so here we need to write code and
we need to read Gadsby IFN blog.
OK, whatever the name of the site you have given.
So now I'm inside this folder and now we need to write and start OK and press enter.
So Gatsby will build the site, so it will take some time.
So here we have localhost eight thousand.
This is where our dev server is going to be and we also have localhost eight thousand four, which slash
and underscore to underscore, to underscore.
These are three in the school and then grad school.
So this is the graphical editor that I'm going to talk about in the future videos.
And we will use this a lot in the schools to create graphical queries.
But for now, we will click on we will copy this localhost eight thousand.
OK, I'll copy this and I'll go to the browser and I'll pasted.
And as you can see, this site is working perfect, so we have successfully bootstrap our application
with Gadsby's.
So now let's move on.
So I'll see you in the next video.