Hello, friends, in this video, we will talk about all the files that were created when we bootstrap
our application with the get subclan, so we need to click on open folder.
And then we need to select our application, which is Gadsby IFN blog.
OK, we need to select the folder and click on Open.
So you are all the files in this folder.
OK, so the folder is Gadsby hyphen blog.
So all the files are in inside this folder that we have created when we bootstrap the project.
So the first one is with me marked on file.
It is a standard marked on file.
It tells you a little bit about how you can start the server and get subclan and a lot of stuff here,
OK?
So you can just read it if you want.
Then we have a package log.
File.
OK.
Then we have a package, Dodgson, and you can see all the dependancy here which are installed for our
application and this is Gadsby stuff.
OK, you have Gadsby image.
That is one which we are going to use to optimize the image, OK?
And Gatsby is actually heavily based on plug ins and it has a lot of plug ins.
If you look at their home page, if you want to do something in your Gadsby site that is probably already
applying for.
OK, so these are some of the plug ins which are installed by Gadsby.
OK, so we are going to talk more about on plug ins later on, so I won't go much into details, OK.
In this lecture.
So Gadsby Saud's filesystem.
OK, so this plug in which we are going to use to source files and this one transform transformer shop.
This one is also used to optimize the image.
Then we have prototypes which is used to verify our props and obviously we have free domain react.
OK, and then we have free helmet and this one is going to handle the stuffs which are in the high tech
on your site.
And then we have dependancy which installed prettier by default, but I have installed prettier in my
code editor.
So if I if you click on this icon and if you type prettier.
So here is the plugin, which I've already installed.
OK, so if you want, you can just search for this plugin and install in your code editor.
OK, so now we have Allscripts.
OK, so these are all the script.
So we have an Barrandov, OK, so once you type and start, this command will be executed and it will
start to get to be website, OK?
It will load the website in the browser.
Then we have Gadsby developed.
So if you type in B.M., if you type in get to be developed, so it will again start the website and
it will all in the browser.
OK, so either you can type and bam start or you can type and bam get speed dial.
So both are the same.
OK, so but we will be using and start so it will run this command and our website will be loaded in
the browser then we have get to be built.
This is to build our website.
OK then we have a but we will not go for testing so mostly we will use NPM start then we have four.
OK, let's go to the all the files.
So I've talked about readme package lock package start Jason then we have Gadsby SSR, dot js and this
is for server side tendering.
So we are not going to use this file in our post, so I will not talk more about it.
And then we have Gadsby hyphen node dodgiest.
This file we are going to use it is, it is in this file we are going to create all the post and pages
programmatically.
OK, so we will get back to that and then we have Gadsby hyphen config Dages.
It is the file where you will set up all your plug ins and the config for the site.
OK, and we will see in this and we will see all this in the coming up lecture's now we have to be hyphen
browser Dages.
So this is the file that we use for the browsers API and we will talk about this later when we will
set up the light and dark more than we have get ignored.
OK, then we have pretty good ignored fruitier that is all about to get.
OK, so now let's go to source folder.
OK, so if I click onto this folder, the era, the folders like component's.
So here are the premade components like ideology's image Dargis OK, and we have CCIS.
So Liotard Sears's.
So if you want to create a component, we will be creating our component in this folder.
OK, so let me closer's then we have image folder so we will copy all our images in this folder.
OK, this is for image.
Then we have four pages folder.
So your all the pages like by default that is indexed Dargis.
So this is all the code that you see and everything inside this page folder, everything inside this
page folder.
Gadsby automatically create a page.
OK, so if you create any page like about Dages so it will be due to this page.
OK, so let me close this closes then.
We have public folder.
So once your site is completed, then it will go in this public folder.
And of course we have node modules, OK, and cache folder for that.
OK, so that's the folder structure of all the files in this project.
So now let's move onto the next lecture where we will install the dependency which we need for this
project.
So I'll see you in the next.
We do.