Hello, friends, in this lecture, we are going to install the dependencies need for our website and
we are going to use Magnon as the source for our content on our website.
Then we are going to need a plug in to show the reading time, which tells us the estimate on how much
time the article will take to read.
We will also use state opinions to create this style for our website.
So that is also a dependency that we need to install.
So first, let's start with the Magnon.
So let's go to the official website, which is Gadsby just dot com and we need to click on Docs and
your inside.
We will click on documentation.
So you're so young you need to click on How to Guide.
OK, so apparently it was open.
So if you click it together and inside this, we will click on.
Routing and pages, and we need to click on how to add content using Mogadon.
OK, so let's click on this.
So your they tell us all about how to make your website work with modern files.
So this documentation is very good.
And if you scroll down, we need something called Gadsby source file system.
This one is already installed as we use the starter when we bootstrap our application so we don't have
to install this.
OK, so then what we need.
So let's scroll down.
So we need this in, OK, Gadsby, Transformers, Remarque, so this is the one which we are going to
install.
They also tell us how to use this plugin, but that I will show you in another video.
OK, so I'm not doing that in this video.
We are just installing the dependancy.
So this is the one which we need to install Gadsby transformer remark, OK?
So let's go to terminal, so I'll go to Israel, to the airport, and I will open the terminal by pressing
control and back to key.
So make sure you are in the right folder.
OK, so mine is going to be hyphen block.
So whatever name you choose for the website, make sure that you are in that folder.
So now what I'm going to do is I'm going to type or maybe I just copy this.
Let's copy this and go back to terminal.
And let's be straight your.
And if you press enter, it will start installing this plugin.
OK, now this plugin has been installed.
So now let's move on and now we will install Retime.
OK, so let's go to the website and let's go to the page like Gadsby, James dot com and here need to
click on plugins and you're going to search for lead.
Dame.
OK, reading time, I think reading this is the one Gadsby, the mock reading that we need to click
on this.
So your other instruction, so they have you on.
But we will use and be installed.
OK, so let me copy this.
And let's go to Visual Studio Code and alert and be in style and I'll paste.
OK, Gadsby, the reading time and I presented.
So this plugin is also being installed now we need to install side company plugin.
So let's go to the website and we need to write style component.
OK, get people against you.
Let's click on this so there is a line of code which we need to install.
So first, there are three things which we need to install.
The first one is Gadsby, plug in Styrofoam and then we have state competence.
And then we need to be able then we need people plug in state.
So let's copy the entire line.
And let's go to Italy, to the airport and your old bastard.
OK, and presented.
So now this is also being installed.
So these were the plug ins, which we need for this project, so let's type and be and start to start
our environment.
OK.
So and boom, start and then press enter.
OK, now our website is running on localhost eight thousand, so I think it is already here.
So let me refresh.
OK, so our site is working fine.
Oh, so that is great.
So we have installed everything which we need for this project.
So let's move on and I'll see you in the next video.