And this we do we will set up our plugins for our project, so we need to go to Gadsby IFN config,
dodgiest file and we will close the site, but OK, so that you can see the code properly.
So let's change the title here.
OK, so your average right gets Gadsby.
Blog.
OK.
And your description, I will change it.
I was right, Gadsby.
Tutorial.
Site.
OK.
And I'll save it and I'll keep it as it is this description, you can write whatever you want, you
can keep whatever description you want, whatever title you want, you can keep it.
And also you can change it.
But keeping as it is.
So this is the site metadata, OK?
And then we have the property for plug in and plug in is going to be in.
OK, so you can add as many plug in as you want.
So first we have Gadsby plug in React Palmach so that one is already set up for us.
So after this I will press enter and I will add a key and we need to write the name of our plug in,
which we have installed.
So a very Gadsby hyphen plug in.
Nathan stai Ivan component's.
This is the plugin which we have installed to Stihler component, and we need to add a comma, so that
is all we need to start our company.
Then we have a plugin called GameSpy Source File System.
Then you have some options that you want to provide for your plug in.
You can create an object like this, OK?
And there's always a property value type, the plug in name, and then you have option property where
you also provide an object with the option that is set for the specific plugin.
But if you don't have any options, then you can type it like this as a string as I did it here.
But now we are going to have options because we are going to set up the file system to source our data
from modern file.
So this plug in your Gadsby source file system with that plug in, you can tell Gadsby where you have
the file you want to use in your site.
And in this case, OK, they are setting up the images folder.
And underscore, Vietnam is something that you have in order to get the current directory name and they
have set up the folder in the source and the source of our images so you can check.
So those images and here will be the images.
OK, so this is the part for images source and in Texas we have a folder for images and we can do the
same to set up the folder where we have our markdown files.
So in this case, I will copy this code.
So let's copy this for.
And I'll press enter an old bastard, OK, remember to add up on my OK, otherwise it will be harder.
And you we need to change that and we need to change the name to content.
OK, so I need to give the name of the folder content and copy this.
And also we need to start the same thing.
Let me save this file and in source folder we need to create a folder content.
So let's create this folder right away.
So contact.
So in this folder, we will have all our modern files.
Right now it is empty, but we will add to markdown files in the coming up like this.
Then we also have the plugin that will make all the Maldon files work for us, and that's the Gadsby
Transformer remark that we have installed.
So we need to create a new object.
OK, so you're idea.
Create a new object.
And your eye light is all.
And back and I write the name of plugin, which is Gadsby.
I often former.
I have some remarkable.
OK.
Alabama.
And we need to write options.
Roland, and once again, we need to add an object and we need to give the property as plugin.
OK, it is plug ins and we are going to set up some plug ins for these plug ins.
OK, so as we have installed plug ins for reading time, so in the options object, we can have a property
of plug in.
OK, and then we have an eddy.
So let's add an array and all.
We need to add about back key and we need to write the name of logging, which is Gadsby.
I often remark.
I assume reading.
Let's save this, so this plug in Gadsby hyphen, transformer hyphen Remarque will transform all our
modern find suitable HTML in our project.
OK, and this plug in Gadsby hyphen Remak.
I find reading from time will help us to display their time.
So we have successfully set up the plug ins.
So these are the plug ins which we need for our cause.
And we have also created the folder named Content.
And inside this, that will be my confidence again that I so in the coming up lectures.
Now let's go to Temenos.
So I'll press Tantallon back to Key and let's start the development environment by typing and beam start.
So I think we have done a mistake.
So yeah, we need to add up.
OK, let's say this now it will run so and be in stock.
OK, now let's go to the let's go with this.
But and let's go to the browser of the year.
So let me refresh so the site is working fine, which means we have installed all the plug ins correctly.
So this is it for this video.
And I see you in the next video.