Hello, friends, in this video, I will show you some tricks that will make development little bit
easier when creating components and importing them with the act.
So if you look inside, index charges file so you can see where we import the component, they are using
it with a relative.
But so we always have to type forward slash competence, slash layout, or if you are in a deeper subdirectory,
you have to type forward slash, dot, dot, forward slash.
And as you can figure it out, it can become a little bit annoying, to be honest.
So we are going to configure Gadsby to be to use absolute input.
That means we can type it like this so we can remove all this dot, dot, forward slash.
But just before the conference, and we need to save this fight, so this will be an absolute import,
we will configure Gadsby with that, but it will also look into SC Fulda.
That's why we can type out component and forward slash layout.
So let's move ahead and then we need to go to Gadsby IFN or G.S. and Gadsby hyphen.
No Doges file is the file that Treneman gets people to your site and you can read more about it by going
to this.
You are.
So let's go to the browser and let's visit their website.
So if you go to this Othell on their website, as I mentioned before, you can use the file if you want
to create dynamic pages.
OK, so Utica's written in the text.
You can use it to create pages dynamically.
OK, and we will also going to use it to add nodes in graphical.
OK, so this file is very important to create dynamic pages and to create nodes and draftable.
So if you want to read more about it so you can just go through this page.
So we will create dynamic pages and Nojin craftspeople in my upcoming videos in the future videos.
OK, but for now, I'm going to use this file to set up a webpage when Gadsby created a config.
Now they have another page.
So if you will do this, you all let's be just dot com slash stocks, slash how to forward slash custom
configuration, slash add custom config, OK.
So if you want to search this file, you can just go to documentation and you're in to that is an option
of customization for tool.
And all you need to click on how to add custom, Bapak.
OK, so you will end up on this page.
So as you'll see, they have something for everybody in the documentation you want to do something.
And they probably covered it in this documentation.
OK, so it's great.
So we have this instruction here.
What we want to do is we want to create absolute input.
So they have a section for that.
So let's scroll down.
So what is the section for this absolute import?
And it tells you all about how you should do it here and when Gadsby is creating your site and building
your site, you can export the function that's going on, create that one thing and you call this function
with different argument.
OK, so the first one is state and the second one is action.
So we are going to use action.
So they distribute it out there.
And then from the actions we can call the sectoral config.
And this is where PAC stuff, OK.
When we set this up.
So if you want to know more about how it works, I will recommend you to read the official.
OK, so this function will take the part sirc OK, the subsea folder and said that as a default folder
for us so we can do absolute import with SLAC folder as Obie's.
So now let's go to results from your code and remove this.
OK, and here we will add a newcomer upcoming for.
Absolute.
Imports and we to export.
And the name of the function is on three.
Funfest.
OK, which is equal to and we need other entities and inside we look at a daily basis and inside that
we will.
So here we are restructuring OK to action.
So actions and then we need an arrow function and inside this function and from our actions.
We have something called said.
The fact.
Config.
And inside those identities, we will take an object, and inside this we will give a property which
is called Resul and it will have an object and then we have module's.
And this is a very big stuff.
So I won't go into details on the big stuff here because it will take too long to explain them.
OK, so now Module's will have an array.
So first we have to resolved and inside this parenthesis we will at the store underscore the name.
And this is a directory which we are working in, so it's an old stuff and we sent it to ASIC.
So you're right, Foma and ASIC.
And the second element in our editor, we set it to No one does four more deals.
Like that, and then we have a comma, but let's save this file, and that is one more thing we need
to do as we are using pot.
So you're at the top, OK, before the summit at the top of the file, we will create a contest and
name it as so that we will take this one centimetre spot, which is equal to require.
And we need to step out and this part is something which is built in with notes so we can require that
one.
OK, so that's everything we have to do to set up absolute input.
So let's save this, see if we go to index charges.
So we have already moved forward slash.
So now this is an absolute import during the next Dargis.
So now we need to open the terminal by pressing control and key.
Let's stop this by pressing controls and then we will start over by writing and then start.
So we are getting some air.
Let's go to let's be.
I know dodgiest fighting Assad, see?
You're just giving me an issue, so let's see what is the subsidy is not defined.
OK, so you're we need.
Quotation mark.
OK.
And also we need double quotes, so let's see this and now let's run it again.
So control C and B and start.
So now it is the site that's built.
So let's go to the browser and check if I refresh, so everything is working fine.
So now this will make our development much easier.
We don't have to type forward slash all the time to, well, inputting the component.
So this is it for this lecture.
And I see you in the next video.