And this we do.
We will create a global stage for our components because we have some states that we want to have all
over the site and style component, have something to help us with that.
It is a function that is called create global styles that we can import from that library.
So we will import that one and use it for global styling.
And the first thing, we will create all the colors for our site and different teams.
And that's what we are going to do in this video.
So let's start so inside the SABC folder, we will create a new folder and name it as styles.
OK, so.
Slides and press enter and inside the slides folder will we will create a new file and give the names
global.
Styles Dargis.
And inside this file, we will write in both.
Curly braces create global style, OK, only style, not styles from style components.
So this is a function which we are going to import from this celebrity style components, then we need
to import fonts.
OK, so I have downloaded the font so you will get it from the resources and just download it and use
it.
OK, so this is the these are the phones to fonts which are required.
So I just copy this.
I just copy this and I create a new folder inside SAAC folder.
So.
Let's create a new folder and name it as font and inside, I need to paste it so.
So let me drag it here.
OK, so these are the two points.
OK, let me close this now, I'm going to import this.
Fonts, so import.
And the first one is Nuni to.
Regular.
OK, so these are two fronts, one is the need to regulate, and one is Ninetto Black.
So you need two regular from.
Font's Shlash, New Nito.
I am regular.
OK, so new to hyphen regular.
Make sure you spell it correctly, OK?
And the second one is enfold.
You need to.
Black.
It's from Fonds.
You need to.
Nathan Black.
Let me check it out, OK, Minuto hyphen black.
OK, we need to get the extension to the.
The.
OK, let's save this, and now we will create JavaScript object with our colors, so we will export
that so that we can import it wherever we want in our application.
So export const.
And we need to give the name of the constant with just colors.
OK.
And then we'll trade the object and you're going to give the properties Cyesis properties, OK, the
first one is white, so the color for white is ash for OK, then we need to give them OK.
So make sure to have karma because this is a JavaScript object.
So semicolon will not work or comma will work.
OK, so now the second property of the.
Which is going to be harsh.
When a.
When see 20.
OK, now the third one is deep, dark green and.
The hash and the hash code is four zero.
Four zero zero zero.
OK.
Make sure to give karma.
OK, so now Blue Shade of Blue Shade one, which is going to be hash.
Two, one five.
Nine, seven, three.
Blue Shade.
To find the color code will be six F eighty six, and the last one is Blue Shade.
Three and the color code will be as Daewon.
Even and know, OK, let's save this.
So these are the colors that we are going to use for our site.
Now let's move on to create the object for different teams.
OK, so you're right, exposed.
So we have two teams on our website.
One is like team, and the second one is the team.
So we will create two object for photos that we can use later when we switch teams.
OK, so this one.
So I first had a great team.
So team and your inside the object.
I like the colors, OK.
And these are the colors which we have created here.
So first one is background.
Colors start dark gray, OK, from the colors we will grab.
This is the one which we have created, OK?
And the second one is menu background.
So that will be colors, dark blue, shade one, OK, then we have text dark, which is going to be
colors, dark blue shade to.
Then we have text mean.
He is going to be colors start new.
Shade, too, to OK, this is shade tree and this is shade to let me save this.
And then we have the last one, we just secondary.
Which is going to be Beller's.
Not blue.
Sheild.
Three.
OK, so let's save this file and now let's copy this entire code and let's based it down below here
and I'll give like a team.
OK, so life team and the background will be white.
So white, OK, and main background will be shade three.
Then next talk will be one and text main will remain the same and secondary will be.
Deep, dark gray.
OK, let me save this, so that's it for our light team.
So we are going to use this object later when we switch the team and I'm going to show you how to use
them.
And in the next lecture, we are going to create the actual spaces for our global standing.
So this is it for this video.
And I'll see you in the next video.