I love this section is 30 section, if you already know what this smackdown and what is graphic and
then you can skip the section.
So I will start with my.
So what does Magdala so ureters.
What is Mogadon?
So I just read this three lines.
This will make you understand what is Mogadon then I'll show you that.
OK, so let me read this out.
So my is a plain text formatting Syntex aimed at making writing for the Internet easier.
The philosophy behind backdowns is that plain text document should be labeled without missing everything,
but there should still be way to add text modified like list bold, etc..
It is an alternative to i w i g.
What do you see is what you get editor which usually takes that letter gets converted to property.
And so this editor, if you use WordPress you will find this kind of an editor.
OK, but if you use my phone and let's say if you want to make a word for what you have to do is you
have to add stick before and after this word so it will become OK.
So I have a I don't need to go to the table of contents.
If I click on that.
Let's say if you want an actual text, you just need to add a hash, OK, if you want to tag and just
need to add to hash.
OK.
Then.
Let's take what is emphasis, emphasis, as as I told you, if you want to make something bold, you
just need to a straight before and after this word or you can just add on the line before and of this
word.
And this is four identical and this is for border to stick, to speak to underlings, to underlings.
And you can just combined with Astrachan, underline, underscore, and you can use this for strikeout.
OK, then you follow the example.
We can just take it out, then you have the list or the list.
Another list.
We can just go through this, then you have links.
OK, then you have images.
So if you want to use inline image, you just need to add exclamation square because there have been
architects and before, after that there will be the you are locked up image.
OK, so you have other examples.
And then you can even have a table.
OK, so you can just go through this to choose.
OK, so let me show you something.
Let's see if I go to my results through Bellport.
Ed.
And let me put it on the beach a little bit afterwards, let's say if you want an actual time, you
just need to attach.
This will be at one.
OK, so this will convert converted into something like this.
And that family will get clean water like this.
This will be one.
When you inspect and see that, you will see this is actually.
OK, something like this, let's say if you want to back then you need to add to hastag and then this
will be.
It's too dark.
So this will be convert something like this adds to this, really added to that.
Again, that be.
So something like this, and if you want something in paragraph, then that's a.
We just need to type.
And this, too, will be the battleground this week, onward, both the things into paragraph.
Well, this next.
Will be converted, something like this.
In my don't file, you just need to write this way and in that statement, it will be an order to something
like this.
OK, so this is the beauty of Monkton, so I hope you understand what ASMOF down and how to use it.
So this is for this video and I'll see you then.
Next, would you like me to do this?
Thank you and goodbye.