Hello, friends.
Welcome back.
In this video, I will create a modern fight required for our project.
So inside content for the day right now, despite empty.
So inside this folder, I did a new file and I lamingtons about God and my and disdain for Mukden.
So my gun files as an extension of empty.
So first we will create front market.
What is front open to let me go to the bazaar.
So as you can see, front my telephone, my daughter dying, my gun fights.
So when you create a modern fight, you can include a set of keys.
And you bet that can be used to provide additional data relevant to specific pages.
And that will tell you this data is front fundamental and is denoted by the triple dash at the start.
OK, and at the end of the block.
So we need to be to the place at the top and at the end of the block, this block will be placed by
a good speech as well as a front marker.
So this is the plug in which we have installed.
So it will be placed by this plugin as a front of the graphical API will provide the key value better
as data in the company.
OK, so we need to create something like this.
OK, this is an additional information for the page.
So like the title, we can give out the image.
OK, so let's do it.
Do a full.
And you're a. to triple dash.
OK, and triple digit and I will write the first one, this type of.
So now the killer has to prove.
OK, so one thing you need to keep in mind is that after the polling, you need to give space if you
don't give space.
And if you're right, let's say that type of speech.
So you can see the entire thing is an audience.
So you need to give us space, too, so you will not get an edit.
OK, the first one is type and then we have paid.
So that is the date format is important.
So first we need to go with the.
So you is 2020.
OK, then hyphen and then the month someone else and then hyphen and the date.
OK, so in my case, today is twenty seven.
So twenty seven.
OK, now the third one is images.
OK, so you can give me images or image, whatever you want.
You can even give Imja.
OK, so this this can be anything, whatever you want to give, OK?
But this is important.
So please keep that in mind so you can give whatever name you want.
If you want to keep it image, you can keep it image and image.
Then for image I will give dot org slash.
Majors slashed and this image we need to create about IFN image, OK?
That is no image about an image started between my majors folder so that I can now select.
That will be page or maybe you can keep about.
Love, you can keep it manually or you can create dynamically.
So in our course, we will create dynamically, but still I will keep it as it is.
But in my upcoming lectures, I will show you how to create dynamically.
OK, then we have the.
Of which can be aboutus beach, OK?
So let's say this, and now we have the content from our goal, so let's go to the browser and I need
content, so I just typed.
So this is our weekend music part of it, so let's copy this.
And so this will be considered as a paragraph.
OK, then I want to back so rehashes and then I'll read this.
Is.
And it's three.
OK, then again, I need some paragraph, so I think go up with this.
So automatic gunfire is ready for about a space of about a space, so this is it for this video and
I'll see you in the next video.