Hello, friends, in this video, we will see what this graph so grad school is a query language and
a lot of people talk about it and some says it will replace the EPA.
But the EPA widely used all over the world for different projects and it's not going anywhere soon.
So I will not tell you who only learned cool.
Because in the real world, you are most likely to work with the EPA depending on what project you are
working.
But school is great and it will be popular in the future.
And Gadsby uses graph internally to query for data.
So we will use Graph Girl when we want to get some data, for example, from our own fight.
So here is some intro text about graph you.
If you want, you can read it.
If I scroll down here, it looks a lot like Jason object.
You need to specify your data and you get better data.
So this is graph tool query and you get it back as a Jason and it has exact same structure and it is
very easy to work with data in your application.
So this is all about the graph.
We will use graph a lot in this post.
So this is it for this video and I I'll see in the next.