Hello and welcome back.
And this video, we will see what a different type of credit to render our data in order to render our
data.
We have three options.
We have static, we have beachbody and we have static ready.
So in this case, I will not be too static, very competent, because this is an old way of rendering
the data.
I will show you, Beachbody, and you started getting used to the query is added back at 15 Bandaranayake
who came out.
And the only difference between page query and you stratigraphy is that in page query we can use variables
so we can have dynamic variables.
But a new static, you cannot have a dynamic variable as the name of this static query.
OK, so this is it for this video and I'll see you in the next video.