Hello, friends, in this video, we will see the graphical editor, so when you start your development
environment in Gadsby, you also get the graphical editor to use.
So this is the you are where you can find the graphical editor.
So let's copy this.
You are in and let's go to the browser.
And yes, I pasted.
OK, so this is the graphical editor, so this is how it looks.
OK, so how does it work?
So in the left here, you have the explorer.
You can have data of all the queries that you can use on your Gadsby site.
And also you have some documentation.
OK, so you can also see the queries that you have here.
This is everything you can query on your site.
And this editor is used very widely in graphics.
So let's close this right now.
It does not work for us.
So this explorer is very easy to use.
For example, if you want to create our own data so we can go to we can go inside all my data, all
my remark, OK, and insert this.
We get data back in something called it just OK.
And then we have nodes.
So let's take on node and then we can select what data we want to query for.
In this case, I want to query for XHTML and it's OK.
And this is for all Monkton files.
As you can see, it pulls the query automatically and this is what graph Google query looks like.
It is very similar to adjacent object.
So and it will follow the same structure as the data you get back in your JSON object.
Now let's press the button.
So as you can see, we get the data back.
That's in our Monkton file.
OK, so this is very neat way to query your data.
You can test geographical queries before you use them in your code.
So this is all about graph Ed.
We will use it more in our course.
So this is it.
And I'll see you in the next to.