Hello, friends.
Welcome back.
So before we start coding, let's talk about style.
So this is the official website where you are in this style IFN components, dot com.
So style component is a label that uses CCIS in JavaScript.
So it helps us to use a system.
It helps to create a component, just like we create the component interact.
OK, but this component will have their own style and we can use it in our just days.
OK, so it will make your code look clean and it is really neat to use it in the combination, which
is.
So they have some example in this case they have created a button, a button confident, and then we
call the style function and then we import the style that has a property.
In this case it is the ETEC and then we have the template letters.
OK, so these are the template letters.
It starts here and it's Enzio.
And inside this we can use our regular Cyesis, we can write our regular synthesis.
And one more important thing that you have inside component that you can have props for then.
OK, so.
It is really easy to change stuff with different additions, depending upon the props that we send in
to our company and we will do in our course.
So, as you can see, they have created a competent but incompetent and that if you scroll down, they
have used this button component in the disks.
OK, just like the regular company.
And it is actually if it is attacked, but instead of attack, they have replaced it with a button thumbprint.
So it will act as a bullet.
But all the styles of which we have given you will be applied on this button.
OK, on this attack or you can follow this was a brief intro, a little bit of control of this.
We will be using more in our post.
And this is it for this video.
And I will see you in the next video.